Artist: Radiohead, ID: a74b1b7f-71a5-4011-9441-d0b5e4122711
{'artist': {'id': 'a74b1b7f-71a5-4011-9441-d0b5e4122711', 
'type': 'Group', 'name': 'Radiohead', 'sort-name': 'Radiohead', 
'country': 'GB', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 
'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}, 'begin-area': {'id': 'd840d4b3-8987-4626-928b-398de760cc24', 'name': 'Abingdon-on-Thames', 'sort-name': 'Abingdon-on-Thames'}, 'isni-list': ['0000000115475162'], 'life-span': {'begin': '1991'}, 'release-list': [{'id': 'ca1306a2-1064-4998-a919-ee123fffd7e2', 'title': 'Radiohead', 'status': 'Promotion', 'quality': 'normal', 'packaging': 'Cassette Case', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1991', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1991', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '66df698a-7944-3251-b3f6-b62461fedecd', 'title': 'Drill', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1992-05-05', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1992-05-05', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '0724388000567', 'asin': 'B001PCNZCC', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'false', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '117cc2ee-4eba-4f28-90cb-91121ca747bf', 'title': 'Drill', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'packaging': 'Slim Jewel Case', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1992-05-05', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1992-05-05', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '0724388000529', 'asin': 'B001FAUN0G', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '9986a0f6-31f2-3917-8695-2c42c8da8ca8', 'title': 'Drill', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1992-05-05', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1992-05-05', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '0724388000543', 'asin': 'B001PCNZCC', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'false', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': 'ed118c5f-d940-4b52-a37b-b1a205374abe', 'title': 'Creep', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1992-09-21', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1992-09-21', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '724388023429', 'asin': 'B000EHLKNU', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '82567d26-bdd6-433d-b2dc-cf896ef9d9ab', 'title': 'Creep', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'date': '1992-09-21', 'country': 'XE', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1992-09-21', 'area': {'id': '89a675c2-3e37-3518-b83c-418bad59a85a', 'name': 'Europe', 'sort-name': 'Europe', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['XE']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '724388023429', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '9a25b959-2a36-32ee-a0ef-d94f050ed4ab', 'title': 'Drill', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1992', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1992', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'asin': 'B001PCNZCC', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'false', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': 'c24fd4e7-d513-4b59-a492-48fe0fff2738', 'title': 'Creep', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1992', 'country': 'US', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1992', 'area': {'id': '489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98', 'name': 'United States', 'sort-name': 'United States', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['US']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '077774493246', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': 'ef561e76-4e77-4950-b8fb-05b3085938db', 'title': '1992‐11‐11: Huddersfield University, Huddersfield, UK', 'status': 'Bootleg', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1992', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1992', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'false', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '37539a5b-7788-4542-a29c-03eb64f63d93', 'title': 'Radiohead', 'status': 'Promotion', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng'}, 'date': '1992', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1992', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '93289500-c47c-4d24-ba69-36b349470ed6', 'title': 'Anyone Can Play Guitar', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-02-01', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-02-01', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '724388044424', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '07aab296-9a40-42a9-8d1f-6b06aa032e8a', 'title': 'Pablo Honey', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'disambiguation': 'made in UK, PM 520', 'packaging': 'Jewel Case', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-02-22', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-02-22', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '077778140924', 'asin': 'B000002UR7', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '286912b9-24d1-4073-9f0d-b03cffad61f8', 'title': 'Pablo Honey', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'disambiguation': 'printed in EU, made in Italy', 'packaging': 'Jewel Case', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-02-22', 'country': 'XE', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-02-22', 'area': {'id': '89a675c2-3e37-3518-b83c-418bad59a85a', 'name': 'Europe', 'sort-name': 'Europe', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['XE']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '077778140924', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '8125fd6f-addc-45a8-ba34-4b023aeae962', 'title': 'Pablo Honey', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'disambiguation': 'made in UK, PM 520, candy CD', 'packaging': 'Jewel Case', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-02-22', 'country': 'XE', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-02-22', 'area': {'id': '89a675c2-3e37-3518-b83c-418bad59a85a', 'name': 'Europe', 'sort-name': 'Europe', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['XE']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '077778140924', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '3d17069b-194f-4f08-921a-b3d7e8fc3c53', 'title': 'Pablo Honey', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'packaging': 'Jewel Case', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-02-22', 'country': 'US', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-02-22', 'area': {'id': '489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98', 'name': 'United States', 'sort-name': 'United States', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['US']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '077778140924', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': 'b1a9b282-7f04-4d14-9aea-bcd2b33e3156', 'title': 'Pablo Honey', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'packaging': 'Cardboard/Paper Sleeve', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-02-22', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-02-22', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '077778140917', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '14cfcdbc-d037-4d46-bfe4-53e6ba36658f', 'title': '1993‐04‐02: Roxane, Tel Aviv, Israel', 'status': 'Bootleg', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-04-02', 'country': 'IL', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-04-02', 'area': {'id': '03691455-bb46-37e3-91d2-cb064a35ffcc', 'name': 'Israel', 'sort-name': 'Israel', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['IL']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'false', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '241499cc-ab40-40c6-8847-fdecf293857a', 'title': 'Pablo Honey', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'packaging': 'Jewel Case', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-04-20', 'country': 'US', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-04-20', 'area': {'id': '489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98', 'name': 'United States', 'sort-name': 'United States', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['US']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '077778140924', 'asin': '5555926987', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '7b3d649d-8fd3-4b0d-a26e-8e0d89d69683', 'title': 'Pablo Honey', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'packaging': 'Jewel Case', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-04-20', 'country': 'CA', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-04-20', 'area': {'id': '71bbafaa-e825-3e15-8ca9-017dcad1748b', 'name': 'Canada', 'sort-name': 'Canada', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['CA']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '077778140924', 'asin': 'B000002UR7', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'false', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '1de7d4b5-4174-4419-b30c-6cf9a6e36de2', 'title': 'Pop Is Dead', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-05-10', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-05-10', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '724388060967', 'asin': 'B005C8RURG', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': 'a08551c1-2e43-4b4c-9d56-d049cdc506d6', 'title': 'Pop Is Dead', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'packaging': 'Slim Jewel Case', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-05-10', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-05-10', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '724388060929', 'asin': 'B001CYHMSQ', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': 'e0da3e07-c79f-4710-a782-0f7e052eae45', 'title': 'Pop Is Dead', 'status': 'Official', 'quality': 'normal', 'packaging': 'Cassette Case', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-05-10', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-05-10', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '724388060943', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'true', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': 'b4d64c83-8051-4089-b118-bad189ca7d5c', 'title': '1993‐06‐04: Magasinet, Göteborg, Sweden', 'status': 'Bootleg', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-06-04', 'country': 'SE', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-06-04', 'area': {'id': '23d10872-f5ae-3f0c-bf55-332788a16ecb', 'name': 'Sweden', 'sort-name': 'Sweden', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['SE']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'false', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': '8c856abb-028e-4f4e-8173-cceab317db04', 'title': '1993‐07‐14: The Arsenio Hall Show, Paramount Studios, Los Angeles, CA, USA', 'status': 'Bootleg', 'quality': 'normal', 'packaging': 'None', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-07-14', 'country': 'US', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-07-14', 'area': {'id': '489ce91b-6658-3307-9877-795b68554c98', 'name': 'United States', 'sort-name': 'United States', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['US']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'barcode': '', 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'false', 'count': '0', 'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}, {'id': 'ae1d8b7c-ef05-41f6-8df8-e1156f2e9d21', 'title': '1993-09-02: Signal Radio Studios: Cheshire, UK', 'status': 'Bootleg', 'quality': 'normal', 'text-representation': {'language': 'eng', 'script': 'Latn'}, 'date': '1993-09-02', 'country': 'GB', 'release-event-list': [{'date': '1993-09-02', 'area': {'id': '8a754a16-0027-3a29-b6d7-2b40ea0481ed', 'name': 'United Kingdom', 'sort-name': 'United Kingdom', 'iso-3166-1-code-list': ['GB']}}], 'release-event-count': 1, 'cover-art-archive': {'artwork': 'false', 'count': '0', 
'front': 'false', 'back': 'false'}}], 'release-count': 1107}}